Hello friends, add me and
welcome if you are new to this channel then you
must like and subscribe and also press the
bell button and talk about your treatment
now we are talking about insurance company your
insurance company yesterday there is an insurance
company its result is its name is
ICICI it has been going on for a long time today's talk is wrong
so let's see today's chart button
so see today's chart pattern friends
today it has given a return of 1% one middle
aged on one side we have subscribed to watch a video so
its
obscene
Dhund
appointment committee
appointed forest officer
if you
subscribe then this stop channel
subscribe to me so friends see friends
see the net profit in 2019
after the results of 104 Dhund came and the
profits
of the accused increased
so in December Twenty20 there was a
net profit of 314 crores which by number
became 2163 then it decreased further in June
more net profit topic
Kaliyug you can definitely do it and
subscribe subscribe
602 increased to 60
subscribe
whatever is less  Yes, you should
go by 2050 and do something special, when
companies are reducing, then there are very good
companies, you can definitely open more solutions in this
and for a long time, it is a very
good topic and on insurance, so because of this,
people got shifted here and their condition became like that of two robbers,
due to which people started subscribing, so
subscribe to it, friends, if you liked this video then do
like and share it and
Kaliyuga, so friends, if you liked this video then do
like and